webdesignmash.com 2018-05-11

# Privacy Policy - Website Design Inspiration | Web Design Resources & Tips | Web Design Mash

This User Agreement and Privacy Policy governs each website, mobile site,  and/or other service associated with Web Design Mash (by any domain, including webdesignmash.com, designblend.co.uk, or any related domain, hereafter referred to as Web Design Mash) regardless of how distributed, transmitted, published, or broadcast (each, a “Service”) provided by (“we,” “us,” or “our”) that links to this agreement, which is binding on each person or entity which accesses or uses this website or collective or websites , whether acting as an individual or on behalf of an entity, including you and all persons, entities, or digital engines of any kind that harvest, crawl, index, scrape, spider, or mine digital content manually or by an automated process or otherwise (collectively, “you” or “your”).

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third-party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>[](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Web Design Mash has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third-party advertisers.

#### Other Cookies

Cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as log-ins. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for the purpose of reference. We do not link any information we store in cookies to any personal information you have submitted.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent cookies can perform activities such as storing your password so you do not have to sign in every time you visit those areas. While these cookies may be used to enable us to track and target the interests of our users so as to enhance the overall experience of using our site, they cannot be used to identify you or access your identity or personal information.

We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any advertisers on our site.

**Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, Web Design Mash will never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18.  
Children under 18 are not allowed to access our service without the knowledge and permission of their parents.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting Web Design Mash, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. This information is collected by Google Analytics.

**Links to third-party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own. This includes log-in and social media integration with Facebook, Twitter, etc.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.
